[Applause]
a Young Nation a multitude of
possibilities a billion opportunities
struck in their Prime hoping for a
better
tomorrow now is the time when India
fights back the road to recovery is here
on February 1st the union budget will
make India bounce back stronger than
ever before this is the budget of Hope a
budget that that will turn hols into
reality the union budget 2022 budget of
[Music]
Hope investments in Securities Market
are subject to Market risks read all
related documents carefully before
investing subscribe to our YouTube
channel and click on the Bell icon to
never miss an update from ICICI
Direct